## CONTACT

- +91 88708 06660
- ✓ ishaak815@gmail.com
- Nungambakkam, Chennai.
- https://mohamedishaak05. github.io/portfolio/

#### **EDUCATION**

2019-2021

## AYYA NADAR JANAKI AMMAL COLLEGE

- Master Of Science
- GPA: 7.72

2016-2019

## SRI.S.RAMASAMY NAIDU MEMRIAL COLLEGE

- Bachelor of Science
- GPA: 6.3

## **SKILLS**

- LARAVEL
- CODEIGNITER
- PHP
- VUE JS
- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- JQUERY
- AJAX
- JSON
- BOOTSTRAP
- MySQL
- AWS (EC2,S3)

# **LANGUAGES**

- Tamil (Fluent)
- English (Intermediate)
- Arabic (Basic)

# MOHAMED ISHAAK.K

## WEB DEVELOPER

#### **PROFILE**

Experienced as a Web developer with a demonstrated history of working in the financial service industry projects. Proficient in Software development, API creation and Designing. Constantly upgrade my knowledge and skills and make a difference in whatever I do. I will be applying my knowledge to build my career and also growth the company development, which will make a positive impact on people's life.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Align Associate

**2023 - PRESENT** 

Web Developer

- Developing the financial & Operational Modules using Laravel.
- Doing well Database management, Query optimization in MySQL.
- Working on ERP dashboards using Vue JS.
- Developing Employee Service Portal in HRMS project with Mobile responsive using Vue.js and Elixir.
- Handling individual projects with our client's requirements.
- Working on FTP automation Scheduler process using Quantum.
- Excellent problem solving and logical thinking to develop the new modules.

#### Priyas Hub Pvt Ltd

2021-2023

Software Engineer

- Developing Dynamic websites using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript.
- Developing a Backend projects Using PHP and Codelgniter.
- API creation for the Mobile App development using Laravel.
- Worked in international payment gateways Like GCC & RBS.
- Handling and working an individual Laravel Web-App project.
- Worked Third-Party API's Like meTopup & POS.
- Hands on experience in AWS(EC2,S3) and Push notification using ECM
- Developed the Ecommerce order tracking system using Laravel.

#### **DECLARATION**

I hereby declare that all the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge.

Place: Chennai

Date:

Signature (K.MOHAMED ISHAAK)